- How else...?
- No, no, no.
(Penny:)How else was I supposed to say it?
(Leonard:)Slowly. Like putting a new fish in a tank.
You don't just drop it in.
(Leonard:)You let the bag sit in the water
a while.
(Sheldon:)The horror.
- Sheldon, I'm sure it's gonna be fine.
- No, it's not going to be fine.
(Sheldon:)Change is never fine.
They say it is, but it's not.
Okay, did you even know the people
that are moving out?
(Sheldon:)I never met them.
(Sheldon:)That's what made them perfect.
(Sheldon:)There were no awkward hellos
in the halls.
There's no clickety-clacking
of high-heel shoes on hardwood floors.
(Sheldon:)They may as well have been a family of cats
just jumping around from drape to drape.
And without that annoying
ammonia-urine smell.
(Penny:)I'm sure the new people
will be just as quiet.
(Sheldon:)You can't know that.
How can you possibly know that?
(Penny:)You're right, I can't. You know what?
Anyone could rent that apartment now.
(Penny:)An opera singer, the cast of Stomp.
(Penny:)Yeah, a tap-dancing pirate
with a wooden leg.
(Leonard:)Why are you making it worse?
(Penny:)I tried making it better,
he wouldn't go for it.
[INAUDIBLE]
- You're right. That's a great idea.
- What?
(Howard:)I'll take the apartment.
I can finally get away from my mother...
(Howard:)...and we can all spend
some more time together.
(Howard:)If you catch my drift.
(Sheldon:)The horror.